Who says you can't achieve your fitness goals while indulging I am here
to share my secret
recipe The Acacia Berry Breakfast Plan decked out in
nutrition The perfect pairing for you But what's even
better is Aditya Birla Sunlife
Insurance Param Suraksha You get health
and wealth by protecting yourself with a term
plan and high returns of a ULIP that too
with rider benefits Get parallel
security with life cover A high age 30
times Picture this Invest 1 lakh every
year for 12 years and you can get up to
more than 50 lakh returns So secure your
family's future and grow your wealth Who's
darling who said you can't have it all With this
plan you get access to exceptional
investment opportunities
like the Nifty Alpha 50 Index Fund that
not only safeguards but delivers
impressive growth Just like the luxurious
toppings at my expense The plan offers five
investment strategies and 19
Exclusive fund options so you can
relax and watch your wealth
grow There are more premium allocation
charges you give up front Offer double the
returns from the 10th year to the 13th year
plus mortality charges Your return at
twin
value will take off and here is the berry on
top With systematic withdrawal facility you can
access your funds any time as per your wish
This plan is absolutely smooth just like my
experience and easy to prepare Say bol chalo I am
going to enjoy my guilt free
breakfast for your balanced portfolio Don't
forget to call your ABSL I
Advisor now